## PROFILE

Design assistant turned web developer with a strong sense of curiosity and drive to get things done. Experienced in working in fast paced environments with a wide variety of people and working with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and Node.js.

## SKILLS

- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- · Node.js & Express.js
- UI/UX Design
- APIs (RESTful & Postman)
- SQL & NoSQL Databases
- React, Redux, Bootstrap, ¡Query
- · Responsive Design
- AJAX & JSON
- Mobile Development (React Native & Expo)
- Test- & Behavior-Driven-Development
- Functional & Object Oriented
  Programming
- Git Version Control
- Strong Communication
- Organization
- Time Management
- Problem Solving
- · Prioritization Abilities
- Crisis Management
- Project Management

# EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

# FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER | CAREERFOUNDRY

July 2022-February 2023

- Intense project based program focused on JavaScript, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools.
- 800+ hours of hands on training with guidance from industry leading developers.

#### ESTHETICIAN | STATE OF FLORIDA

June 2009-Present

### VALENCIA COLLEGE

August 2007-May 2009

#### PALM BEACH STATE COLLEGE

August 2006-May 2007

## EXPERIENCE

### INTERIOR DESIGN ASSISTANT

API Draper | Palm Beach, Florida January 2018-March 2020

- Collaborated with Lead Designer to bring clients design visions to life by sourcing products and preparing materials for production.
- Helped clients visualize design solutions that aligned with their taste, space, and budget.
- Created functional, safe, and aesthetically pleasing spaces by assessing space requirements, determining optimal placement, and selecting decorative items.

#### MOBILE SPRAY TAN ARTIST | ESTHETICIAN

Self-Employed | Jupiter, Florida February 2010-Present

• Providing clients with quality, color-matched, in-home Norvell spray tanning.

#### **RETAIL SALES SPECIALIST**

Macy's | Palm Beach Gardens, Florida June 2009-June 2011

- · Managed Benefit Cosmetics in-store sales counter.
- Formed relationships with clients by providing superior customer service and expert skin-care and make-up recommendations.
- Exceeded daily sales goals in a competitive retail environment to become a Star Seller.